<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eat This Radio</title>
    <link>http://eatthisradio.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eat This Radio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Eat This Radio 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://eatthisradio.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Synth melodies</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/bastiaan_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/bastiaan_1/</guid>
      <description>Mechanizedmind a.k.a. Bastiaan is a regular contributor to and co-founder of Eat This Radio. Catchy synth melodies are the star of this episode. Ranging from Fridge to The Space Lady.
 Fridge - Ark Broadcast - Belly dance Beak&amp;gt; - Eggdog Boards of Canada - Reach for the dead Sleep party People - An iris Pseudocorus Anika - I go to sleep Nine Circles - Twinkling stars Position Parallel - Comme ca Ruth - Polaroid roman photo The Space Lady - Major tom  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mechanizedmind #2</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/bastiaan_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/bastiaan_2/</guid>
      <description>Mechanizedmind a.k.a. Bastiaan is a regular contributor to and co-founder of Eat This Radio. In this episode Bastiaan heads out to explore the depths of spaced out guitars, hushed voices and melancholic melodies.
 Kikagaku Moyo - Fata Morgana Amp - Polemic Flying Saucer Attack - The Season Is Ours Amp - Lightdripglow Windy &amp;amp; Carl - Undercurrent Roy Montgomery - The Soul Quietens Landing - Scenes Upon The Trees Tara Jane O&amp;rsquo;Neil - The Louder Jessica Bailiff - One Red Year Grouper - STS Felicia Atkinson - Infant Vampire William Basinski - Melancholia I  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The synthesized Häpna Books</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_2/</guid>
      <description>Wouter van Veldhoven build a name with his performances with tape recorder, self build instruments and analogue synthesizers. Wouter will explore the depths of music in eclectic shows full of experiment. Wouters second show focusses on the wonderful Häpna label and affiliated music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_1/</guid>
      <description>Wouter van Veldhoven build a name with his performances with tape recorder, self build instruments and analogue synthesizers. Wouter will explore the depths of music in eclectic shows full of experiment. This first show, fittingly called Things, Wouter serves you a mix of experimental music of all sorts.
 Francoise Bayle - La fin du bruit: éros rouge David Toop - Sea Slug Taylor Deupree - Minism Lou Harrison - Concerto In Slendro: II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pingpong #1</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/pingpong_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/pingpong_1/</guid>
      <description>pingpong are collaborative mixtapes. Each show features another opponent who&amp;rsquo;s family, friend or hero (or all). Alternating contributions unfold into expeditions, collisions, constructions and awe.
Episode #1: LN / Bastiaan
 Richard Skelton - Noon Hill Wood Lichens - Swarmed (Live) King Krule - Czech One 4Carla dal Forno - The Garden Scout Niblett - Uptown Top Ranking Ex-Easter Island Head - Four Guitars Ignatz - Dead by Noon Crescent - Abstract Forms Holy Sons - Station ID #1 Gowns - Feathers The Iditarod - Older, not wiser  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Eat This Radio is a platform for alternative music made by music lovers. We bring you mixes made by us, our friends and heroes. There is no regular schedule, we add new mixes when we get them. Check back on this website or follow us on Facebook
Eat This Radio is made by:
Bastiaan Verhage
LN
Wouter van Veldhoven
With many thanks to:
Michaala Jung
Ingo
Robhar</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>