<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post on Eat This Radio</title>
    <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post on Eat This Radio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://eatthisradio.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Songs for when you&#39;re snowbound [..]</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/boduf_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/boduf_1/</guid>
      <description>Mat Sweet, a.k.a Boduf Songs has been making amazing music over the years. He joins Eat This Radio with a great mix with an amazing name (that sadly doesn&amp;rsquo;t fit in the title) so we&amp;rsquo;ll just put it here.
Enjoy listening to &amp;ldquo;Songs for when you&amp;rsquo;re snowbound and supplies are getting low and the only other person there goes out for help and you have a feeling they won&amp;rsquo;t be coming back and you&amp;rsquo;re ok with it&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MFR #12</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/mfr_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/mfr_1/</guid>
      <description>Moving Furniture Records from Amsterdam has been building an impressive catalogue of quality releases over the years. We are happy to welcome Sietse van Erve on Eat This Radio, sharing some of his favorite tracks!
 Jospeh Kurdika - Downer Catherine Lamb - Matter/Moving (3) Eliane Radigue - Occam III Radboud Mens &amp;amp; Matthijs Kouw - A Phill Niblock - Parker&amp;rsquo;s Altered Mood, AKA, Owed To Bird Sarah Davachi - Burgundy Kassel Jaeger - Retroaction 2- Non-controlled Aerial Feedbacks Triac - Across  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eat this records #2</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/carlos_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/carlos_2/</guid>
      <description>Carlos returns for the second part of the Eat This Records special. Again he dove into history and came back with this amazing mix. Excellent music!
 Koolfonk - Ilsa Loden - Vlugt (and more for you) Swap - NN rmx Gimmik - NN rmx Gosub - NN rmx Legowelt - discobitch EOG - NN rmx d&amp;rsquo;Enborage - Capacitor Math - Water (enwaded) Mitchel Akiyama - Spiral jetty Metal Beast- Upcgriqr (L&amp;rsquo;usine rmx)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pingpong #4</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/pingpong_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/pingpong_4/</guid>
      <description>pingpong: collaborative mixtapes. each episode features another opponent who&amp;rsquo;s family, friend or hero (or all). alternating contributions unfold into expeditions, collisions, constructions and awe.
episode #4: LN / popgunpirates
 golden diskó ship - wake/sleep [LN] raccoo-oo-oon - visage of the fox [pp] evangelista - in animal tongue [LN] coh (feat. little annie) - curious yellow [pp] the books - if not now, whenever [LN] balmorhea - bowsprit [pp] pretend - some how [LN] volcano!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>through sleet and snow</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/johan_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/johan_2/</guid>
      <description>Johan returns with a second mix for Eat This Radio. Inspired by commuting through collective traffic through nasty Swedish winter weather Johan takes us on a dark cold journey. Dress up warm for this mix!
 Nortt - Af Döde Jaap Vink - Granule American Cloud Songs - Solar Initiation Colin Stetson - Home Marc Ribot - Bateau Arnold Dreyblatt - Group Velocity Damon Albarn and Michael Nyman - Colquhoun’s Story (excerpt) Wreathes - The Reigns Radik Tyulyush- Oskys Urug Alasdair Roberts - Dighty Kassel Jaeger and Jim O’Rourke - Wakes On Cerulean (excerpt) Yair Elazar Glotman - Retenant Oren Ambarchi - Song Of Separation part 2 Nathan Moody - Sapphire John Frusciante - Cut Myself Out  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the lower frequency spectrum</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_6/</guid>
      <description>Wouter explores the depths of sub bass and low frquency sounds. Dive in and enjoy!
 Thomas Köner - Ilira Mika Vainio - hallitaajuus Emptyset - Body Francisco Lopez - El Dia Anterior A La Emergencia De Los Adultos De Magicicada Annea Lockwood - turning gong Beatrice Dillon - A Different River Once (excerpt) Annea Lockwood - deep water gong Oren Ambarchi - Fever, A Warm Poison Zeno van den Broek - Canon 1 - excerpt - Paranon Farmers Manual - Macro Woeb David Toop - Ancestral Beings, Sightless by Their Own Dust Phill Niblock - Stosspeng I Daniel Menche - He was One and Many-2512764980 Sunn o))) - alice  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eat this records #1</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/carlos_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/carlos_1/</guid>
      <description>We are proud to give you the first of two mixes by Carlos Kok, the founder of the wonderful Eat This Records. Carlos takes you through the catalogue of what once was and what still is amazing! A total of two hours of underground electronic music that made a difference. Sit back and remember:)
 Kalle Dawidson - NN Quick and bright - Super bmx Funckarma - NN Endorphins - Jeth Math - Hex Legowelt - Berlin Ostbahnhof Orgue electronique - Lullaby Loess - Lull Mitchell Akiyama - Her summer has only days Loden - A better landing Quench - Corb L&amp;rsquo;usine - NN Endorphins - c64lprom  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gruizig en prettig</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_5/</guid>
      <description>A collection of songs, things and other things
 Woelv / Genevieve Castree / O Paon - Aéroport / Évolution Baka People - Hut song John Cale - Trance #2 Basil Kirchin - Primitive London VI My Bloody Valentine - Lose My Breath Lawrence English - Cemetery Gate Hobart Australia Soccer Committee - Blessed Sarah Davachi - For Voice (edit) Ghédalia Tazartès - Reviens Os Mutantes - Fuga #2 (edit) The free design - If I were a carpenter Nico - Le petit chevalier Roj - Attaining the Third state Pierre Bastien - X (R6) II Zi[L] Basil Kirchin - Once upon a time (excerpt) Doris - You Never Come Closer Broadcast - Teresa, Lark of Ascension Roberto Musci - Katak Dance for H Partch Tony Caro and John - Eclipse of the Moon Basil Kirchin - Primitive London IV Keith Fullerton Whitman - Schnee Linda Perhacs - Parallelograms Steve Roden - this is for everyone who wants to dance Mountains - bay Vashti Bunyan - Winter is Blue The Focus Group - Make Way Tape - Golden Twig Brigitte Fontaine - Brigitte  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pingpong #3</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/pingpong_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/pingpong_3/</guid>
      <description>pingpong: collaborative mixtapes. each episode features another opponent who&amp;rsquo;s family, friend or hero (or all). alternating contributions unfold into expeditions, collisions, constructions and awe.
episode #3: LN / Dan4Evers
 mirah - 100 knives [LN] cat stevens - the first cut is the deepest [D] tara jane o’neil - new harm [LN] dinosaur jr. - feel the pain [D] trash kit - medicine [LN] shockabilly - when you dream about bleeding [D] young people - forget [LN] four one and only’s - completely nude between forgetmenots [D] grass widow - cover you [LN] andy shauf - wendell walker (live at the drake hotel) [D] picastro - the stiff [LN]  pingponged nov-dec 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>do while</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/bastiaan_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/bastiaan_3/</guid>
      <description>Cut up, looped, endless music. Bastiaan dives into music based on loops from very subtle background loops to slowly shifting patterns that will hypnotise you. Best played on endless repeat! (artwork by Katya Sannikova)
 Es - A love cycle Saule - Hola Akira Rabelais - And the permanence of smoke or stars Es - Les fleurs son des bonnes audtrices Giuseppe Lalesi - 08 Fennesz - Before I leave Kyoka - Toy planet Oval - Do While  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>drawing music from the ether</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/johan_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/johan_1/</guid>
      <description>Johan G Winther joins Eat This Radio with a wonderful mix that fits well this time of the year. Spring is almost there, that&amp;rsquo;s how this mix sounds like. Meditative like the winter with bright sounds that announces spring. Enjoy!
 Eliane Radigue - Usral (April 1969) Delia Derbyshire - The Pattern Emerges Micheline Coulombe Saint-Marcoux - Moustières Else Marie Pade - Illustrationer Kong Vinter Lydia Kavina - Free music no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hit me with your rhythm brick!</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_4/</guid>
      <description>Wouter returns with a collection of people playing rhythmic things that are strange, straightforward or both&amp;hellip;
 Ella Jenkins - Rhythm Instruments: Rhythm Sticks
 Louis Andriessen - Hoketus
 Yowie - Ineffable Dolphin Communion
 OOIOO - UMA
 Galina Ustvolskaya - Composition II Dies irea V &amp;amp; VI
 David Lang - Cheating, Lying, Stealing
 Ella Jenkins - Different Rhythms
 Moondog - Single Foot
 Brigitte Fontaine - Comme a la Radio</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rêves et mémoires</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/amp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/amp/</guid>
      <description>Amp have a long history in music. They formed in the 90&amp;rsquo;s as part of the immensely creative Bristol scene along side bands such as Flying Saucer Attack and the Third Eye Foundation. We are delighted they joined Eat This Radio with a eclectic mashup compiled by Richard Amp. A mix full of memories of what was and dreams what can be. Over an hour of sonic explorations!
 Excerpt from Jeff Wayne’s War Of The Worlds Programme - Une Vie (edit) Stockhausen - No 12 Kontakte (1959&amp;frasl;1960) excerpt BBC Sound Effects Record - No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pingpong #2</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/pingpong_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/pingpong_2/</guid>
      <description>pingpong: collaborative mixtapes. each episode features another opponent who&amp;rsquo;s family, friend or hero (or all). alternating contributions unfold into expeditions, collisions, constructions and awe.
episode #2: LN / Marion [LN’s mom]
 william onyeabor - better change your mind [LN] keimzeit - zukunft [M] colin stetson + sarah neufeld - won’t be a thing to become [LN] the notwist - your signs [M] björk - the anchor song [LN] pj harvey - water [M] young people - fly seagull fly [LN] radiohead - weird fishes / arpeggi [M] mount kimbie - delta [LN] zero 7 - red dust [M] d33j - park [LN]  pingponged okt-nov 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>delicate structures</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/rutger1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/rutger1/</guid>
      <description>Rutger Zuydervelt has been active in the music scene for quite some time now under his monniker Machinefabriek. For eat this radio he compiled a mix full of delicate sounds, almost complete silences. Please close your eyes, listen and take this musical journey with Rutger Zuydervelt.
 Jürg Frey - Extended Circular Music No.2 (performed by Philip Thomas) Steve Reich - Come Out Film - Out of Doors Giuseppe Ielasi - untitled Jabu - Tomb Yastaki Shimizu - Bridgestone 4 Nicola Ratti - r40 Erik Satie - Vexations (performed by Alan Marks) Ueno - untitled Ton - Mi AM/PM - The Ends (2) Jazzkammer - Pulse Jabu - Searc Jürg Frey - Extended Circular Music No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spring break downer vibes</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wim1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wim1/</guid>
      <description>Wim_morc dives into lo-fi, chansons and anything that will kill your Spring Break mood. We are very pleased with this wonderful collection of songs. After finishing this mix Wim told us already he has new ideas for more. We can&amp;rsquo;t wait!
Wim_morc runs the wonderful Morc tapes label. The label has produced a steady stream of beautiful releases that are all worth checking out. Beside that he also makes music as Circle Bros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a collection of pulses</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_3/</guid>
      <description>Pulses, bleeps and patterns are the focus of this impressive mix by Wouter. Ranging from the early fifties to now this mix gives a comprensive overview into experimental electronic music through the past 60 years. Sit down and enjoy!
 Geiger Counter - Kraftwerk Canon - 3, Super Addere (excerpt) - Dick Raaijmakers data.triplex - Ryoiji Ikeda Mechanical Motions - Dick Raaijmakers Band 5: Rhythmic Variation - Daphne Oram Three Single Sounds Taken In Canon i - Daphne Oram Winkel Pong - Ursula Bogner The Dead Past - Robert Aiki Aubrey Lowe Themes II - Rashad Becker En phase / Hors phase - Bernard Parmegiani Minuut 5 - Machinefabriek Uviol - Autechre Interzone Bureau Desk - Robert Aiki Aubrey Lowe Les Traces D&amp;rsquo;un Pont - Benjamin Lew The Rhythm Modulator - Raymond Scott Toc - Komet Automatic Ping - Keith Fullerton Whitman Deuxième série: polyrythmie - François Bayle Ole - nebulo Gamelan - Maggi Payne Drums - Laurie Spiegel Liquid Energy - Brian Hodgson, Delia Derbyshire, Don Harper Toy Funk - Raymond Scott Softgrid - Richard Scott Rhythmic Variations i - Daphne Oram Hahmo - Pan Sonic Module 6 - Alva Noto  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>günther #1</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/gunther_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/gunther_1/</guid>
      <description>Regular guest Günther kicks off with a mix full of avant-garde and exprimental music. Ranging from drone experiments to industrial mixed with a healthy portion of wave.
 Lemon Kittens - Rome Burning Nurse With Wound - Ketamineaphonia This Heat - Twilight Furniture Popol Vuh - In den Gärten Pharaos Lines - The Landing Factory Floor- Bipolar Wipers- When It&amp;rsquo;s Over  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pingpong #1</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/pingpong_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/pingpong_1/</guid>
      <description>pingpong: collaborative mixtapes. each episode features another opponent who&amp;rsquo;s family, friend or hero (or all). alternating contributions unfold into expeditions, collisions, constructions and awe.
episode #1: LN / Bastiaan
 richard skelton noon hill wood [LN] lichens swarmed - live [B] king krule czech one [LN] carla dal forno the garden [B] scout niblett uptown top ranking [LN] ex-easter island head four guitars [B] ignatz dead by noon [LN] crescent abstract forms [B] holy sons station id #1 [LN] gowns feathers [B] the iditarod older, not wiser [LN]  pingponged okt-nov 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hushed voices</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/bastiaan_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/bastiaan_2/</guid>
      <description>Mechanizedmind a.k.a. Bastiaan is a regular contributor to and co-founder of Eat This Radio. In this episode Bastiaan heads out to explore the depths of spaced out guitars, hushed voices and melancholic melodies.
 Kikagaku Moyo - Fata Morgana Amp - Polemic Flying Saucer Attack - The Season Is Ours Amp - Lightdripglow Windy &amp;amp; Carl - Undercurrent Roy Montgomery - The Soul Quietens Landing - Scenes Upon The Trees Tara Jane O&amp;rsquo;Neil - The Louder Jessica Bailiff - One Red Year Grouper - STS Felicia Atkinson - Infant Vampire William Basinski - Melancholia I  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>günther #2</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/gunther_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/gunther_2/</guid>
      <description>Günther continues with a second mix for Eat This Radio. This time flirting with noise, industrial, drone and everything that comes along the way.
 Dance Disaster Movement - I Want Your Sass Laddio Bolocko - Nurser Pink Industry - Time For Change Slowdive - Changes TEARIST - Disposition Leisur Hive - Try To Be Still Swans - Real Love Tropic Of Cancer - Be Brave Lebanon Hanover Gallowdance M Nilson- I hope You Die Karen Lawrence - I Won`t stop The holydrug couple - counting sailboats 13Arif Sag - Su Samsunun Evleri  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the synthesized häpna books</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_2/</guid>
      <description>Wouter van Veldhoven build a name with his performances with tape recorder, self build instruments and analogue synthesizers. Wouter will explore the depths of music in eclectic shows full of experiment. Wouters second show focusses on the wonderful Häpna label and affiliated music.
 Fantomoj de la Vitro Domo - Robert Aiki Aubrey Lowe See-Through - Arthur Russell Cyclic bit - Raymond Scott Il, Les Quitta A L&amp;rsquo;Aube - Benjamin Lew, Steven Brown You&amp;rsquo;ll never be alone - The Books Quiet Industry - Belbury Poly and Spacedog Ghost Riders in the Sky - The Space Lady Meditation outtakes - The Books Nigatsu - Asa-Chang &amp;amp; Junray Millions of millions - The Books (Chintrap) - Machinefabriek Hikoki - Tenniscoats Sand Dunes - Tape Drowned but survived - The Books How to Behave in Elevators - Musette Zenna &amp;amp; Marie (excerpt) - Hans Appelqvist  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>synth melodies</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/bastiaan_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/bastiaan_1/</guid>
      <description>Mechanizedmind a.k.a. Bastiaan is a regular contributor to and co-founder of Eat This Radio. Catchy synth melodies are the star of this episode. Ranging from Fridge to The Space Lady.
 Fridge - Ark Broadcast - Belly dance Beak&amp;gt; - Eggdog Boards of Canada - Reach for the dead Sleep party People - An iris Pseudocorus Anika - I go to sleep Nine Circles - Twinkling stars Position Parallel - Comme ca Ruth - Polaroid roman photo The Space Lady - Major tom  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>things</title>
      <link>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eatthisradio.com/post/wouter_1/</guid>
      <description>Wouter van Veldhoven build a name with his performances with tape recorder, self build instruments and analogue synthesizers. Wouter will explore the depths of music in eclectic shows full of experiment. This first show, fittingly called Things, Wouter serves you a mix of experimental music of all sorts.
 Francoise Bayle - La fin du bruit: éros rouge David Toop - Sea Slug Taylor Deupree - Minism Lou Harrison - Concerto In Slendro: II.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>